Prescott S. Bush Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Press Releases, undated, 1952-1962
  - Clinton Conference—shore erosion, 1955 April 1 (Box 5:, Folder 237)
  - Rogers/Bush—communism; internal security, 1955 April 10 (Box 5:, Folder 238)
  - Senator Green—Code of Fair Procedures, 1955 April 12 (Box 5:, Folder 239)
  - S. 1657; Grants-in-Lieu, 1955 April 13 (Box 5:, Folder 240)
  - Cannon—shore project appropriations, 1955 April 15 (Box 5:, Folder 241)
  - Shore erosion; CT highway; Grants-in-Lieu, 1955 April 16 (Box 5:, Folder 242)
  - S. 414 hearings; public works, 1955 April 19 (Box 5:, Folder 243)
  - Bush; DuPont; highway, 1955 April 24 (Box 5:, Folder 244)
  - Atomic Energy; shore erosion; S. 414; Democrats, 1955 April 30 (Box 5:, Folder 245)
  - Polish Constitution Day Refugee Relief program, 1955 May 2 (Box 5:, Folder 246)
  - Mental Health Week, 1955 May 4 (Box 5:, Folder 247)
  - H.R.I. passage, 1955 May 6 (Box 5:, Folder 248)
  - Polio; highway; appropriations, 1955 May 7 (Box 5:, Folder 249)
  - Bush/Clay—Highway program, 1955 May 8 (Box 5:, Folder 250)
  - Appropriations Committee—shore erosion, 1955 May 9 (Box 5:, Folder 251)
  - Speech: Taft Memorial Public service, 1955 May 14 (Box 5:, Folder 252)
  - Laundrymen meeting—Highway program, 1955 May 14 (Box 5:, Folder 253)
  - Talbott/Bush; Film-Canel; Middletown, 1955 May 18 (Box 5:, Folder 254)
  - Highway; vaccine; Air Force Academy, 1955 May 20 (Box 5:, Folder 255)
  - Postal pay raise, 1955 May 24 (Box 5:, Folder 256)
  - Weather Bureau appropriations, 1955 May 28 (Box 5:, Folder 257)
  - S. 414 [Hurricane bill], 1955 June 2 (Box 5:, Folder 258)
  - Shore problem; weather bureau, 1955 June 4 (Box 5:, Folder 259)
  - Weather bureau, 1955 June 4 (Box 5:, Folder 260)
  - Bush/Thomas—Navy, 1955 June 5 (Box 5:, Folder 261)
  - S. 441; Federal Minimum wage; Housing legislation, 1955 June 18 (Box 5:, Folder 262)
  - Bush/Fleming; Corps of Engineers; shore problems, 1955 June 19 (Box 5:, Folder 263)
  - S. 1577 In Lieu of Taxes, 1955 July 1 (Box 5:, Folder 264)
  - Bush/Schmidt; Weather Bureau warnings, 1955 July 3 (Box 5:, Folder 265)
  - Prosperity, 1955 July 15 (Box 5:, Folder 266)
  - Waterbury Loyal Order of Moose; Communism and Foreign policy, 1955 July 17 (Box 5:, Folder 267)
  - Shore Protection program, 1955 July 18 (Box 5:, Folder 268)
  - Bicycle; President, 1955 July 19 (Box 5:, Folder 269)
  - Downey meeting at Geneva; Communist China and U.N., 1955 July 28 (Box 5:, Folder 270)
  - Bush/Strauss—Atoms for Peace, 1955 July 31 (Box 5:, Folder 271)
  - Freedom of 11 American Airmen—John Downey, 1955 August 1 (Box 5:, Folder 272)
  - 84th Congress, 1st Session review, 1955 August 2 (Box 5:, Folder 273)
  - 84th Congress overview—Peace and Prosperity, 1955 August 5 (Box 5:, Folder 274)
  - Eisenhower letter to Bush, 1955 August 8 (Box 5:, Folder 275)
  - Rossi letter, 1955 August 10 (Box 5:, Folder 276)
  - Atoms for Peace, 1955 August 11 (Box 5:, Folder 277)
  - Humphrey—tax write-off, Defense Mobilization Office, 1955 August 25 (Box 5:, Folder 278)
  - SBA Office, Waterbury—Charles Foster, 1955 August 25 (Box 5:, Folder 279)
  - Freemen—farm loans to flood victims, 1955 August 26 (Box 5:, Folder 280)
  - PHA action to assist flood victims, 1955 August 26 (Box 5:, Folder 281)
  - Flood Protection program appropriations, 1955 August 27 (Box 5:, Folder 282)
  - Mrs. Leopold Bush, 1955 August 28 (Box 5:, Folder 283)
  - Mayors and Selectmen—Urban Renewal Program, 1955 August 30 (Box 5:, Folder 284)
  - Secretary of the Army—Brucker, 1955 August 31 (Box 6:, Folder 285)
  - President Eisenhower, 1955 September 1 (Box 6:, Folder 286)
  - Flood Protection Project appropriations—Hayden, 1955 September 1 (Box 6:, Folder 287)
  - Johnson/Knowland—Flood Project, 1955 September 2 (Box 6:, Folder 288)
  - Wire—Hotel Bond meeting, 1955 September 2 (Box 6:, Folder 289)
  - General Fleming—Mad River Flood control, 1955 September 1 (Box 6:, Folder 290)
  - Ellsworth Bunker—Red Cross assistance, 1955 September 7 (Box 6:, Folder 291)
  - General Shepherd/Bush, 1955 September 11 (Box 6:, Folder 292)
  - Loan of $10 million to New Haven Railroad, 1955 September (Box 6:, Folder 293)
  - Defense Department—Air Force, Army, Navy, 1955 September 15 (Box 6:, Folder 294)
  - Sec. Weeks—Hurricane and flood warning, 1955 September 17 (Box 6:, Folder 295)
  - Salem, CT barbecue; comprehensive flood control system, 1955 September 17 (Box 6:, Folder 296)
  - Coast Guard Academy examination, 1955 September 20 (Box 6:, Folder 297)
  - Fulbright—Banking and Currency Committee; disaster insurance, 1955 September 21 (Box 6:, Folder 298)
  - Bush/Mitchell; Secretary of Labor, 1955 September 25 (Box 6:, Folder 299)
  - Bush/Folson, 1955 September 26 (Box 6:, Folder 300)
  - Brucker/Bush correspondence, 1955 October 9 (Box 6:, Folder 301)
  - Attorney General Brownell, 1955 October 10 (Box 6:, Folder 302)
  - Governor Peterson/ Bush—water supply, 1955 October 10 (Box 6:, Folder 303)
  - Flood Insurance program—comments, 1955 October 13 (Box 6:, Folder 304)
  - Success Village housing—Bridgeport, CT, 1955 October 14 (Box 6:, Folder 305)
  - Hershey Metal Products loan of $1.8. million, 1955 October 14 (Box 6:, Folder 306)
  - Rowland Hughes, 1955 October 14 (Box 6:, Folder 307)
  - Scott—Department of Agriculture, 1955 October 14 (Box 6:, Folder 308)
  - Air Force contracts in CT disaster areas, 1955 October 17 (Box 6:, Folder 309)
  - Speech: New England Newspapers advertisers, 1955 October 18 (Box 6:, Folder 310)
  - New Britain—Citizen's Committee, 1955 October 20 (Box 6:, Folder 311)
  - Bush/Peterson, 1955 October 23 (Box 6:, Folder 312)
  - P.L. 875, Corps of Engineers—Private water supply, 1955 October 25 (Box 6:, Folder 313)
  - New England Reg. Rivers and harbors, 1955 October 27 (Box 6:, Folder 314)
  - CT Assn. of Insurance Agents: Prosperity, 1955 October 27 (Box 6:, Folder 315)
  - Flood Insurance, 1955 November 1 (Box 6:, Folder 316)
  - DoA—Program for Farmers, 1955 November 2 (Box 6:, Folder 317)
  - Bush/Barnes—Small Business Administration, 1955 November 6 (Box 6:, Folder 318)
  - Middle East Situation, 1955 November 7 (Box 6:, Folder 319)
  - Naugatuck River (Ansonia) channel clearing, 1955 November 8 (Box 6:, Folder 320)
  - Highway damages—proposed amendment, 1955 November 11 (Box 6:, Folder 321)
  - Bush/Peterson—Civil Defense Administration, 1955 November 21 (Box 6:, Folder 322)
  - Staff Study—Federal Disaster Insurance, 1955 December 8 (Box 6:, Folder 323)
  - Republican Leaders' Meeting, 1955 December 12 (Box 6:, Folder 324)
  - Chavez—Public Works program, 1955 December 14 (Box 6:, Folder 325)
  - DoA policy change—$1500 limit, 1955 December 14 (Box 6:, Folder 326)
  - Urban Renewal—Naugatuck, 1955 December 14 (Box 6:, Folder 327)
  - Fulbright—banking programs, 1955 December 15 (Box 6:, Folder 328)
  - CT Delegation, 1955 December 18 (Box 6:, Folder 329)
  - Service academy candidates, 1955 December 24 (Box 6:, Folder 330)
  - Thomaston Dam and Reservoir damages, 1955 December 29 (Box 6:, Folder 331)
  - “Form” speech for re-election campaign, 1956 January 4 (Box 6:, Folder 332)
  - Sponsorship correspondence, 1956 January 4 (Box 6:, Folder 333)
  - State of the Union, 1956 January 5 (Box 6:, Folder 334)
  - Flood Insurance bill, 1956 January 5 (Box 6:, Folder 335)
  - Flood legislation, 1956 January 5 (Box 6:, Folder 336)
  - Emergency Feed Grain Program: CT eligibility, 1956 January 9 (Box 6:, Folder 337)
  - Flood program, 1956 January 15 (Box 6:, Folder 338)
  - Budget message, 1956 January 16 (Box 6:, Folder 339)
  - Education bill, 1956 January 18 (Box 6:, Folder 340)
  - House Appropriations Committee statement, 1956 January 19 (Box 6:, Folder 341)
  - Quinnipiac Council B.S.A. priority, 1956 January 19 (Box 6:, Folder 342)
  - WTIC; Natural Gas Bill; education, 1956 January 20 (Box 6:, Folder 343)
  - Middle East situation, 1956 January 26 (Box 6:, Folder 344)
  - Harris-Fulbright bill, 1956 January 27 (Box 6:, Folder 345)
  - School; area development; housing for elderly; flood bill, 1956 January 30 (Box 6:, Folder 346)
  - Flood Insurance bill, 1956 January 31 (Box 6:, Folder 347)
  - Senate Appropriations statement, 1956 February 2 (Box 6:, Folder 348)
  - WTIC—Highway program, 1956 February 2 (Box 6:, Folder 349)
  - Congressional Delegation, 1956 February 3 (Box 6:, Folder 350)
  - General Itschner correspondence, 1956 February 6 (Box 6:, Folder 351)
  - Deficiency bill statement, 1956 February 8 (Box 6:, Folder 352)
  - Lincoln Day speeches, 1956 February 8 (Box 6:, Folder 353)
  - Torrington schedule, 1956 February 11 (Box 6:, Folder 354)
  - Bush/Brownell—education, 1956 February 12 (Box 6:, Folder 355)
  - Fleming, 1956 February 17 (Box 6:, Folder 356)
  - Gas Bill veto, 1956 February 17 (Box 6:, Folder 357)
  - Immigration and Farm bill, 1956 February 17 (Box 6:, Folder 358)
  - S. 3272 Floor statement, 1956 February 23 (Box 6:, Folder 359)
  - Bush/Cole—housing and flood insurance, 1956 February 26 (Box 6:, Folder 360)
  - Polish National Home; Sadlak; Immigration bill, 1956 February 27 (Box 6:, Folder 361)
  - Adlai Stevenson, 1956 February 27 (Box 6:, Folder 362)
  - Unemployment correspondence, 1956 February 29 (Box 6:, Folder 363)
  - S. 3272; Farm, housing, Old age assistance, 1956 March 2 (Box 6:, Folder 364)
  - S. 2861, S. 2853, S. 3272, 1956 March 7 (Box 6:, Folder 365)
  - ICC Arpaia, 1956 March 8 (Box 6:, Folder 366)
  - New Haven Railroad meeting), 1956 March 11 (Box 6:, Folder 367)
  - Emergency feed grain, 1956 March 11 (Box 6:, Folder 368)
  - Bush/Lindsay—immigration, 1956 March 11 (Box 6:, Folder 369)
  - Flood Commission hearings, 1956 March 12 (Box 6:, Folder 370)
  - Arpaia—New Haven Railroad, 1956 March 15 (Box 6:, Folder 371)
  - WTIC—flood hearings; House appropriations; Senate public works, 1956 March 16 (Box 6:, Folder 372)
  - New England Senators' correspondence, 1956 March 19 (Box 6:, Folder 373)
  - Bush/Taft—Ireland, 1956 March 26 (Box 6:, Folder 374)
  - Unemployment Compensation benefits, 1956 March 27 (Box 6:, Folder 375)
  - Garrett; Farm; Mayor Lee; UR; Indemnity Flood Control bill, 1956 March 29 (Box 6:, Folder 376)
  - S. 3272—Rhode Island resolution, 1956 April 9 (Box 7:, Folder 377)
  - Garrett—Civil Rights, S. 3272, 1956 April 13 (Box 7:, Folder 378)
  - Farm bill veto, 1956 April 17 (Box 7:, Folder 379)
  - Flood Control bills, 1956 April 18 (Box 7:, Folder 380)
  - Urban Renewal—House subcommittee, 1956 April 19 (Box 7:, Folder 381)
  - Dr. Hauge—economic condition, 1956 April 23 (Box 7:, Folder 382)
  - DPA—Bennett Amendment, 1956 April 24 (Box 7:, Folder 383)
  - DPA Bennett Amendment statement, 1956 April 25 (Box 7:, Folder 384)
  - Bennett Amendment; Flood Insurance bill; other disaster bills, 1956 April 26 (Box 7:, Folder 385)
  - Gore bill—highway, 1956 April 29 (Box 7:, Folder 386)
  - Flood Insurance bill—White House Amendment, 1956 May 1 (Box 7:, Folder 387)
  - Highway bill—action by Public Works, 1956 May 4 (Box 7:, Folder 388)
  - Flood Insurance bill Amendment, 1956 May 4 (Box 7:, Folder 389)
  - “Nothing without Labor” Litchfield dedication, 1956 May 5 (Box 7:, Folder 390)
  - Flood Insurance bill; Grand Lodge of CT, Sons of Italy, 1956 May 6 (Box 7:, Folder 391)
  - Middle East policy, 1956 May 6 (Box 7:, Folder 392)
  - Fallon bill—highway, 1956 May 7 (Box 7:, Folder 393)
  - Loyalty Day celebration, West Haven—FBI; Simon Cohen; Communists, 1956 May 7 (Box 7:, Folder 394)
  - Counter-agents and highway, 1956 May 10 (Box 7:, Folder 395)
  - Federal Flood Insurance Act of 1956, 1956 May 10 (Box 7:, Folder 396)
  - Hoover Commission recommendations, 1956 May 10 (Box 7:, Folder 397)
  - Urban Renewal Administration—Housing bill report, 1956 May 14 (Box 7:, Folder 398)
  - Veteran's Organization—government witnesses trial, 1956 May 16 (Box 7:, Folder 399)
  - Mazzabuffi and Gilman—flood program, 1956 May 21 (Box 7:, Folder 400)
  - Spence—urban renewal assistance for disaster areas, 1956 May 24 (Box 7:, Folder 401)
  - H.R. 10660—highway bill, 1956 May 28 (Box 7:, Folder 402)
  - Freedom Crusade, 1956 June 1 (Box 7:, Folder 403)
  - Bennet Amendment B & C, 1956 June 1 (Box 7:, Folder 404)
  - Garrett—Highway program, 1956 June 6 (Box 7:, Folder 405)
  - “Do Nothing” review of 84th Congress, 2nd session, 1956 June 8 (Box 7:, Folder 406)
  - Flood control; appropriations; New England fiscal 1957, 1956 June 13 (Box 7:, Folder 407)
  - Highway conference, 1956 June 21 (Box 7:, Folder 408)
  - Bennett Amendment—statement, 1956 June 22 (Box 7:, Folder 409)
  - Highway conference report, 1956 June 25 (Box 7:, Folder 410)
  - S. 3272, H.S. 9555, H.S. 9554 correspondence, 1956 June 26 (Box 7:, Folder 411)
  - DPA Conference, 1956 June 26 (Box 7:, Folder 412)
  - Mutual Security Act of 1956, H. R. 11356, 1956 June 29 (Box 7:, Folder 413)
  - American Association of State Highway Officials—commendation, 1956 June 30 (Box 7:, Folder 414)
  - DPA 18 mile limit statements, 1956 July 1 (Box 7:, Folder 415)
  - S. 3272 enactment, 1956 July 2 (Box 7:, Folder 416)
  - Disaster Housing bills, 1956 July 3 (Box 7:, Folder 417)
  - Flood Insurance bill, House Banking and Currency, 1956 July 8 (Box 7:, Folder 418)
  - S. 3272 appropriations, 1956 July 9 (Box 7:, Folder 419)
  - Hartford's Front Market Redevelopment project, 1956 July 10 (Box 7:, Folder 420)
  - Commerce and DMO comments, 1956 July 11 (Box 7:, Folder 421)
  - S. 3272—Ribicoff and Wise, 1956 July 11 (Box 7:, Folder 422)
  - S. 3272 correspondence, 1956 July 11 (Box 7:, Folder 423)
  - Eisenhower correspondence, 1956 July 16 (Box 7:, Folder 424)
  - Bush/McCormack Act appropriations, 1956 July 17 (Box 7:, Folder 425)
  - Cost of Torrington and Winsted dams, 1956 July 19 (Box 7:, Folder 426)
  - Mutual Security Appropriations bill: Knowland Amendment, 1956 July 24 (Box 7:, Folder 427)
  - Disability insurance, 1956 July 26 (Box 7:, Folder 428)
  - 1956 Republican platform, 1956 August 21 (Box 7:, Folder 429)
  - Winsted, CT: “Progress”, 1956 September 28 (Box 7:, Folder 430)
  - Buffumville dam ground breaking, 1956 October 5 (Box 7:, Folder 431)
  - Anti-filibuster—Civil Rights, 1957 January 2 (Box 7:, Folder 432)
  - Rule 22, anti-filibuster, 1957 January 4 (Box 7:, Folder 433)
  - Armed Forces Committee, 1957 January 9 (Box 7:, Folder 434)
  - State of the Union, 1957 January 10 (Box 7:, Folder 435)
  - Steel shortage, 1957 January 10 (Box 7:, Folder 436)
  - Banking and Currency Committee—steel shortage, 1957 January 16 (Box 7:, Folder 437)
  - Election of H. Meade Alcorn, Republican National Committee, 1957 January 22 (Box 7:, Folder 438)
  - Military Academy appointments, 1957 January 30 (Box 7:, Folder 439)
  - Public works; Omnibus bill; Torrington dams, 1957 February 4 (Box 7:, Folder 440)
  - School construction; Torrington dams, 1957 February 7 (Box 7:, Folder 441)
  - Lithuanians—statement, 1957 February 14 (Box 7:, Folder 442)
  - Omnibus Judges bill—Judiciary Committee, 1957 February 20 (Box 7:, Folder 443)
  - Middle East—budget, 1957 February 22 (Box 7:, Folder 444)
  - Middle East resolution, 1957 February 27 (Box 7:, Folder 445)
  - Hartford Urban Renewal project; foreign aid; flood insurance, 1957 March 8 (Box 7:, Folder 446)
  - P.L. 685 Torrington project, 1957 March 9 (Box 7:, Folder 447)
  - State payment of flood costs, 1957 March 18 (Box 7:, Folder 448)
  - Temporary housing for flood victims, 1957 March 19 (Box 7:, Folder 449)
  - State payment of flood costs, 1957 March 22 (Box 7:, Folder 450)
  - Budget cut effects on welfare and flood programs, 1957 April 5 (Box 7:, Folder 451)
  - Acreage allotments for corn, 1957 April 9 (Box 7:, Folder 452)
  - P.L. 685 (Bush/McCormack), 1957 April 18 (Box 7:, Folder 453)
  - Tallamy—Highway program, 1957 April 19 (Box 7:, Folder 454)
  - Government program from Poultry Production and Support, 1957 April 22 (Box 7:, Folder 455)
  - Flood Insurance, 1957 April 27 (Box 7:, Folder 456)
  - Budget defense, 1957 May 2 (Box 7:, Folder 457)
  - Farm programs effect of budget; Flood control program, 1957 May 3 (Box 7:, Folder 458)
  - Public Works appropriations statement, 1957 May 7 (Box 7:, Folder 459)
  - Flood Insurance appropriations, 1957 May 15 (Box 7:, Folder 460)
  - National Science Foundation—earth satellites, 1957 May 17 (Box 7:, Folder 461)
  - Housing bill; Defense appropriations; Atomic energy, 1957 May 31 (Box 7:, Folder 462)
  - Mutual Security Act, 1957 June 14 (Box 7:, Folder 463)
  - Fiscal policies, 1957 June 18 (Box 7:, Folder 464)
  - Senate rules—Talmadge and Javits, 1957 June 19 (Box 7:, Folder 465)
  - Civil Rights, Hells Canyon, 1957 June 28 (Box 7:, Folder 466)
  - Greenwich Chapter, American Red Cross, 1957 July 3 (Box 7:, Folder 467)
  - Democratic leadership; Civil Rights; Waterbury Redevelopment; Bush/McCormack Projects, 1957 July 12 (Box 7:, Folder 468)
  - Billboard control; Drought; Hoover Commission; Soil bank; Civil Rights, 1957 July 26 (Box 7:, Folder 469)
  - Civil Rights, 1957 July 31 (Box 7:, Folder 470)
  - Ribicoff; Farm drought, 1957 August 7 (Box 7:, Folder 471)
  - S. 497 Rivers and Harbors bill, 1957 August 8 (Box 7:, Folder 472)
  - Farm program; FHA; Payments; Silverware, 1957 August 9 (Box 7:, Folder 473)
  - Ribicoff; Farm program, 1957 August 15 (Box 7:, Folder 474)
  - Employment Act amendment, 1957 August 21 (Box 7:, Folder 475)
  - S. 2824; Farm inflation; Flood; 85th Congress, 1957 August 22 (Box 7:, Folder 476)
  - New England Conference of State Federations of Women's Clubs; Education; Billboard; Highway, 1957 September 11 (Box 7:, Folder 477)
  - Annual National Home Week Banquet, Home Builders Association—Inflation housing, 1957 September 20 (Box 7:, Folder 478)
  - West Coast SAC headquarters and missile production inspection, 1957 November 28 (Box 7:, Folder 479)
  - Cordiner Rep. And Unified Command; missile, 1958 January 2 (Box 8:, Folder 480)
  - State of the Union address, 1958 January 9 (Box 8:, Folder 481)
  - New Haven Shrine Club—Reorganization of Defense Department, 1958 January 10 (Box 8:, Folder 482)
  - Cronan, Coar; Defense budget, 1958 January 12 (Box 8:, Folder 483)
  - President's budget message, 1958 January 13 (Box 8:, Folder 484)
  - CT-MA Compact for Thames River Valley, 1958 January 13 (Box 8:, Folder 485)
  - Billboard control bill, 1958 January 16 (Box 8:, Folder 486)
  - Urban Renewal, 1958 January 20 (Box 8:, Folder 487)
  - Reorganization of Defense Department, 1958 February 2 (Box 8:, Folder 488)
  - Unemployment, 1958 February 3 (Box 8:, Folder 489)
  - S. 3209 Unification bill, 1958 February 3 (Box 8:, Folder 490)
  - Air Force and Merchant Marine Academy appointments, 1958 February 3 (Box 8:, Folder 491)
  - East Hartford Rotary—Reorganization, 1958 February 12 (Box 8:, Folder 492)
  - Urban renewal; Thomaston dam, 1958 February 13 (Box 8:, Folder 493)
  - Wethersfield—Lincoln Day dinner, 1958 February 13 (Box 8:, Folder 494)
  - St. Louis—Today's Challenge in Education speech, 1958 February 23 (Box 8:, Folder 495)
  - Education, 1958 February 28 (Box 8:, Folder 496)
  - S. 3429 Highway reimbursement bill, 1958 March 10 (Box 8:, Folder 497)
  - S. 3429 statement, 1958 March 11 (Box 8:, Folder 498)
  - S. 3429 correspondence, 1958 March 12 (Box 8:, Folder 499)
  - Defense Contracts and Mutual Security, 1958 March 14 (Box 8:, Folder 500)
  - New England Flood Protection—appropriations, 1958 March 18 (Box 8:, Folder 501)
  - S. 3429 House public works, highway reimbursement, 1958 March 25 (Box 8:, Folder 502)
  - Gore Highway bill, 1958 March 26 (Box 8:, Folder 503)
  - Navy missiles program, 1958 March 28 (Box 8:, Folder 504)
  - Cape Canaveral, 1958 April 3 (Box 8:, Folder 505)
  - Income Tax Regulations for Teachers, 1958 April 4 (Box 8:, Folder 506)
  - Democratic program on Country's economy, 1958 April 11 (Box 8:, Folder 507)
  - P.L. 71 status; Hurricane protection, 1958 April 17 (Box 8:, Folder 508)
  - Urban Renewal projects in CT, 1958 April 18 (Box 8:, Folder 509)
  - S. 3638, S. 3639; Flood control bills; Torrington dam; Bridgeport harbor, 1958 April 21 (Box 8:, Folder 510)
  - Flood control bills; Defense reorganization, 1958 April 25 (Box 8:, Folder 511)
  - Cronan—Labor legislation, 1958 April 30 (Box 8:, Folder 512)
  - Speech—Defense Reorganization, 1958 May 1 (Box 8:, Folder 513)
  - Polish Constitution Day, 1958 May 2 (Box 8:, Folder 514)
  - S. 3753, bill for Oystermen, 1958 May 6 (Box 8:, Folder 515)
  - S. 3683, Area Development bill, 1958 May 8 (Box 8:, Folder 516)
  - Tax structure and tax cuts, 1958 May 9 (Box 8:, Folder 517)
  - Area redevelopment amendment, 1958 May 12 (Box 8:, Folder 518)
  - Committee on Public Works—Omnibus Rivers and harbors bill, 1958 May 19 (Box 8:, Folder 519)
  - Slum Clearance and Urban renewal programs, 1958 May 23 (Box 8:, Folder 520)
  - Thomaston dam ceremonies, 1958 May 26 (Box 8:, Folder 521)
  - Anti-Nixon riots, 1958 May 28 (Box 8:, Folder 522)
  - Mutual Security Program, 1958 June 6 (Box 8:, Folder 523)
  - Mentally retarded, 1958 June 8 (Box 8:, Folder 524)
  - Graduation education and informed citizens, 1958 June 9 (Box 8:, Folder 525)
  - Resolution on Commission on Ethics, 1958 June 27 (Box 8:, Folder 526)
  - Amendment to Housing bill—Urban renewal, 1958 July 7 (Box 8:, Folder 527)
  - Wooster Square redevelopment, 1958 July 7 (Box 8:, Folder 528)
  - Resolution—mentally retarded children, 1958 July 15 (Box 8:, Folder 529)
  - House bill Trade Agreements, 1958 July 16 (Box 8:, Folder 530)
  - Trade Agreements—Safeguard provisions, 1958 July 17 (Box 8:, Folder 531)
  - Defense Department reorganization, 1958 July 18 (Box 8:, Folder 532)
  - Trade Agreements Act, 1958 July 23 (Box 8:, Folder 533)
  - Humane slaughter, 1958 July 28 (Box 8:, Folder 534)
  - H.R. 8002—Hoover Commission recommendations, 1958 July 31 (Box 8:, Folder 535)
  - Sound Government credit, 1958 August 4 (Box 8:, Folder 536)
  - Keogh bill, 1958 August 12 (Box 8:, Folder 537)
  - House Appropriations Committee action on Conference report, 1958 August 20 (Box 8:, Folder 538)
  - Review of the records of the 85th Congress, 1958 August 23 (Box 8:, Folder 539)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers—Urban Renewal and Redevelopment, 1958 October 13 (Box 8:, Folder 540)
  - American Assembly—Inflation, 1958 October 16 (Box 8:, Folder 541)
  - Bridgeport Redevelopment Railroad Avenue Project, 1958 December 4 (Box 8:, Folder 542)
  - Tax assessment settlement CT/ United Aircraft Corp., 1958 December 4 (Box 8:, Folder 543)
  - Award of $17 million contract to Sikorsky, 1958 December 15 (Box 8:, Folder 544)
  - John S. Cooper nomination for Republican Floor Leader, 1958 December 22 (Box 8:, Folder 545)
  - Copper and Kuchel, 1958 December 30 (Box 8:, Folder 546)
  - Academy appointments, 1958 December 31 (Box 8:, Folder 547)
  - Flood protection project on Byram, Pemberwick, Greenwich (January 9), 1959 (Box 8:, Folder 548)
  - S. 63, Consumer Credit Control; S. 64 Employment Act, Congressional Res. Item veto, 1959 January 9 (Box 8:, Folder 549)
  - Six year Urban Renewal and slum clearance program, 1959 January 13 (Box 8:, Folder 550)
  - S. 267 Recognition of the Polish Legion of American Veterans, 1959 January 14 (Box 8:, Folder 551)
  - Inflation—Russia's Cold War Weapon, 1959 January 14 (Box 8:, Folder 552)
  - President's Budget Message, 1959 January 19 (Box 8:, Folder 553)
  - Toll Road reimbursement, 1959 January 20 (Box 8:, Folder 554)
  - Additional district judges, extra sessions at Bridgeport, 1959 January 20 (Box 8:, Folder 555)
  - Coast Guard Barracks construction, 1959 January 22 (Box 8:, Folder 556)
  - Slum clearance and urban renewal—Bridgeport Chamber of Commerce, 1959 January 27 (Box 8:, Folder 557)
  - Problems before the 86th Congress, 1959 February 2 (Box 8:, Folder 558)